[
  {
    "question": "Important contexts for software architecture defined in the book are:",
    "answers": [0, 2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Business", "Modelling", "Project life cycles", "Technical"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The most important technical factor that contributes to the architecture is...",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": "2015 Kahoot 04: Life Cycle",
    "options": [
      "Architects expertise",
      "Development tools",
      "Stakeholder's goals",
      "Quality attributes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of dominant software development processes are:",
    "answers": [1, 3],
    "exam": "2015 Kahoot 04: Life Cycle",
    "options": [
      "Ad-hoc development",
      "Model-driven",
      "Pair-programming",
      "Waterfall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Analyze requirements",
      "Get requirements",
      "Make business case",
      "Design architecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the second architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Create/Select architecture",
      "Document architecture",
      "Implement architecture",
      "Understand arch requirements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the third architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [0, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Create architecture",
      "Document architecture",
      "Implement architecture",
      "Select architecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the fourth architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [1, 2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Analyze architecture",
      "Communicate architecture",
      "Document architecture",
      "Implement architecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the fifth architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [0, 1],
    "exam": "2015 Kahoot 04: Life Cycle",
    "options": [
      "Analyze architecture",
      "Evaluate architecture",
      "Implement system",
      "Test system"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sixth architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [0, 2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Implement system",
      "Ensure conform implementation",
      "Test system",
      "Quality assurance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the seventh architecture activity in the life-cycle?",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": "2015 Kahoot 04: Life Cycle",
    "options": [
      "Ensure conform implementation",
      "Evaluate architecture",
      "There is no 7th step",
      "Quality assurance"
    ]
  }
]
